(Raj:)You're welcome.
Missy, I'm gonna go get my nails done.
Do you wanna come?
(Missy:)God, yes. Thanks.
(Raj:)You're welcome.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye, Missy.
(Leonard:)Bye, Missy, see you.
- Goodbye, Leonard.
- Yeah, no, bye, Penny.
(Howard:)- You two have to back off.
- Why should I back off? You back off.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, this is my apartment,
and she's my roommate's sister.
- So what? You've got Penny.
- How do I have Penny?
(Leonard:)In what universe do I have Penny?
- So I can have Penny?
- Hell, no.
Excuse me, can I interject something?
(Sheldon:)I'm ordering pizza online.
Is everyone okay with pepperoni?
- Sheldon, can I talk to you in private?
- I guess.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry,
I was going to order you cheese-less.
- Thank you.
SHELDON: It's okay.
(Sheldon:)Lactose intolerance
is nothing to be embarrassed about.
[IN INDIAN ACCENT] I'm a fancy
Indian man. We invented pajamas.